<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement &#8211; Robotoblog</title>
	<atom:link href="https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/tag/simple-modern-green-script-boy-or-girl-birth-announcement/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 05:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/android-chrome-512x512-2-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement &#8211; Robotoblog</title>
	<link>https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Big Deals! Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement</title>
		<link>https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/big-deals-simple-modern-green-script-boy-or-girl-birth-announcement/</link>
					<comments>https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/big-deals-simple-modern-green-script-boy-or-girl-birth-announcement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Birth Announcement Cards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/big-deals-simple-modern-green-script-boy-or-girl-birth-announcement/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Big Deals! Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement</h4>
<p>Big Deals! Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement &#8211; Birth Announcement Cards This item is trending! <i>Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement</i>  good product  <u>Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement</u> You can order itThis simply charming photo birth announcement flat card features a contemporary design that lets you easily customize it to suit your style. We&#8217;ve picked rounded corners that we&#8217;ve chosen as the default setting, but you can easily change the look to sharp corners, as that look also works wonderfully with this design. Scalloped edges might also suit your photo and taste! At the very top, we&#8217;ve added &#8216;HELLO, WORLD&#8217; but please feel free to change that to whatever strikes your fancy, be it &#8216;WELCOME&#8217; or &#8216;INTRODUCING&#8217;, etc. If you&#8217;d like to highlight your gratitude for a gift and make this a thank you card, you can edit it to show &#8216;THANK YOU SO MUCH!&#8217; or similar at the top. And in any case, you can include your gratitude in a short message on the back. This text is in black, and you can change it if you&#8217;d like. In choosing a script for your baby&#8217;s name, we were looking for something informal, with personality but also an orderly flow that&#8217;s easy to read, and we found something we loved. We added an elegant medium dark shade of green to further accentuate this part of the design. Having said this, you can change the color and font of this or any other text according to your own taste. If you prefer a more minimalist look, you can delete without replacing any of our sample stats-you might not want to include the time of day or length, for example. The default color of the text below the name is dark gray. We&#8217;ve set the background on both sides as transparent, to let the color of your paper simply serve as the base tone. You can change this on one or both sides by choosing a color instead, be it a soft blue or pink or anything else. On back, we&#8217;ve added some placeholder text for you to replace with your own message. The default text color is the same dark gray as the date and stats text on the front, but you can change it on either side if you prefer another color. Though we used all upper case for the placeholder text, you can of course change this look, and you can also change the font. After you delete our placeholder text, you might decide to simply leave the back entirely blank, so that you can add a handwritten message with your signatures after you receive your cards. In any case, please do remember to remove all of the placeholder text as well as our sample photo! The default paper type, matte, has a soft warmth to it and resists smudging, so it&#8217;s a great choice for writing your own message. Use the intuitive design tools and your favorite photo and your inspiration to personalize this custom birth announcement flat card and make it uniquely yours! <b>Price:$2.53</b><br /><center> <center></p>
<h1><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f44d.png" alt="ðŸ‘" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/simple_modern_green_script_boy_or_girl_birth_announcement-256517511784730552?rf=238627982471231924">Simple Modern Green Script Boy or Girl Birth Announcement Price ($2.53)</a> </h1>
<p></center> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?q=https://www.zazzle.com/simple_modern_green_script_boy_or_girl_birth_announcement-256517511784730552?rf=238627982471231924"><img decoding="async" src="https://rlv.zcache.com/simple_modern_green_script_boy_or_girl_birth_announcement-r_vscrei_500.jpg"></a></center></p>
<p> Category : Birth Announcement Cards</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://robotoblog.github.io/reviews/big-deals-simple-modern-green-script-boy-or-girl-birth-announcement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
